internet-webhosting.com 2012-06-09

# Malaysia Webhosting, Dedicated Server, Domain Registration & Website Design - PRIVACY

Because protecting your privacy is very important to INTERNET WEBHOSTING, we operate our web site under the following guidelines to safeguard your personally identifiable information:

INTERNET WEBHOSTING policies and procedures for handling customer information have been created with the understanding that Internet technologies are still evolving and that Internet business methods are continuing to evolve to meet the needs and opportunities of the changing technologies. As a result, INTERNET WEBHOSTING policies and procedures are subject to change.

  * What Personal Information does INTERNET WEBHOSTING collect? 

  * Data Security

  * How is customer information used?

  * Will INTERNET WEBHOSTING ever send me direct mailings?

  * How do I protect my Personal Information in public forums?

  * What about privacy on sites that INTERNET WEBHOSTING links to?

  * Disclosure of customer information and communications

** What Personal Information does INTERNET WEBHOSTING collect?**

In the course of serving its customers, INTERNET WEBHOSTING acquires, stores and transmits customer communications and information that customers may regard as private or sensitive. Some of this information - such as the customer's name, address, telephone number, and credit card data - is provided to INTERNET WEBHOSTING by its customers in order to establish service. Other information - such as the customer's account status, choice of services, and customer logs - is created and maintained by INTERNET WEBHOSTING in the normal course of providing service. INTERNET WEBHOSTING also uses cookies, which are small pieces of information that a web site can store in a designated file on a user's computer for various reasons. In addition, INTERNET WEBHOSTING may store customers' electronic mail and other communications as a necessary incident to the transmission and delivery of those communications.

**Data Security**  
INTERNET WEBHOSTING will protect the confidentiality of its customers' information, account information and personal communications to the fullest extent possible and consistent with the law and the legitimate interests of INTERNET WEBHOSTING, its partners, its employees and other customers of INTERNET WEBHOSTING services. To protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of information that is collected from customers, INTERNET WEBHOSTING has appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures in place. 

**How is customer information used?**  
INTERNET WEBHOSTING may share customer information with selected partners, for example, to provide customers with information about products which might be of interest to the customer or to enable the customer to take advantage of special partner programs. INTERNET WEBHOSTING may also use customer information to provide its customers with system information or information about new or upgraded products.

** Will INTERNET WEBHOSTING ever send me direct mailings?**  
From time to time, INTERNET WEBHOSTING may send its customers information about various products and services that may be of interest. We will not send you information of this type without specifically allowing you to "opt out" of such mailings. You can opt out by sending an e-mail to support@internet-webhosting.com, however by doing so, you may miss important communication regarding your service.

In addition, if you are a INTERNET WEBHOSTING reseller, INTERNET WEBHOSTING and/or its partners and advertisers may from time to time send you newsletters, promotional material, and other mailings. You can opt out by sending an e-mail to billing@internet-webhosting.com

** How do I protect my Personal Information in public forums?**  
INTERNET WEBHOSTING may offer interactive forums, such as message boards and chat. INTERNET WEBHOSTING users should be aware that when they voluntarily disclose Personal Information to other users or to third parties on the INTERNET WEBHOSTING system, through e-mail, or outside of the INTERNET WEBHOSTING system, that information can be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited messages from other members or third parties. While INTERNET WEBHOSTING strives to protect your Personal Information, INTERNET WEBHOSTING cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to INTERNET WEBHOSTING, and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information.

** What about privacy on sites that INTERNET WEBHOSTING links to?**  
INTERNET WEBHOSTING may provide links to its partners and other Internet sites. These sites have separate data and privacy practices independent of INTERNET WEBHOSTING, and INTERNET WEBHOSTING disclaims any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.

** Disclosure of customer information and communications**  
INTERNET WEBHOSTING will not otherwise disclose its customers' personal and account information unless INTERNET WEBHOSTING has reason to believe that disclosing such information is necessary to identify, make contact with, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing harm or interfering with the rights or property of INTERNET WEBHOSTING, INTERNET WEBHOSTING customers, or others, or where INTERNET WEBHOSTING has a good faith belief that the law requires such disclosure. 

INTERNET WEBHOSTING also will not, except for reasons stated below, disclose to third parties the contents of any electronic mail or other electronic communications that INTERNET WEBHOSTING stores or transmits for its customers. The circumstances under which INTERNET WEBHOSTING will disclose such electronic customer communications are when: 

  * it is necessary in order to provide service to the customer; 

  * it is necessary to protect the legitimate interests of INTERNET WEBHOSTING and its customers; 

  * it is required to cooperate with interception orders, warrants, or other legal process that INTERNET WEBHOSTING determines in its sole discretion to be valid and enforceable; and 

  * it is necessary to provide to a law enforcement agency when the contents are inadvertently obtained by INTERNET WEBHOSTING and appear to pertain to the commission of a crime. 

  * INTERNET WEBHOSTING disclaims any intention to censor, edit or engage in ongoing review or surveillance of communications stored on or transmitted through its facilities by customers or others. INTERNET WEBHOSTING will, however, review, delete or block access to communications that may harm INTERNET WEBHOSTING, its customers or third parties. The grounds on which INTERNET WEBHOSTING may take such action include, but are not limited to, actual or potential violations of INTERNET WEBHOSTING policies.
